export const htmlQuiz = {
  quiz_name: "HTML Tags",
  quiz_id: 10003,
  quiz_category: "html",
  questions: [
    {
      questionId: 1,
      question: "What does the <a> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines a hyperlink",
        B: "Defines an abbrevation",
        C: "Defines an article",
        D: "Defines underlined text",
      },
      correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
      questionId: 2,
      question: "What does the <img> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines an image upload element",
        B: "Defines an image display element",
        C: "Defines an image import location",
        D: "Defines a set of links where images can be found",
      },
      correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
      questionId: 3,
      question: "What does the <div> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Divides a page horizontally or vertically",
        B: "Defines a military division like the 1st Cavalry Division",
        C: "Defines a generic container for content",
        D: "Defines a divider to split the page in half",
      },
      correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
      questionId: 4,
      question: "What does the <p> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines a print-friendly section of a page",
        B: "Defines a picture",
        C: "Defines a paragraph",
        D: "Defines a digital representation of a person",
      },
      correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
      questionId: 5,
      question: "What does the <ul> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines a link to unstructured content",
        B: "Defines a list that is not ordered",
        C: "Defines multiple list items",
        D: "Defines a group of content",
      },
      correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
      questionId: 6,
      question: "What does the <table> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines a grouping of tabular data",
        B: "Creates a structured layout for organizing content in a grid format.",
        C: "Allows for the embedding of multimedia elements within a content area",
        D: "Defines a section of content that can be formatted for presentation",
      },
      correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
      questionId: 7,
      question: "What does the <span> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines an element that spans the entire width of the page",
        B: "Defines a Spanish translation of English text",
        C: "Defines a generic inline container for phrasing content",
        D: "Defines an element that connects two div elements like a bridge",
      },
      correctAnswer: "C",
    },
    {
      questionId: 8,
      question: "What does the <h1> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines an incremental health bar element for internet games",
        B: "Defines the first level of section headings on a web page",
        C: "Defines the header navigation bar seen on most websites",
        D: "Defines the first document metadata header",
      },
      correctAnswer: "B",
    },
    {
      questionId: 9,
      question: "What does the <footer> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines the web page footer section",
        B: "Defines a section that contains page numbers on a PDF document",
        C: "Defines the length of paper required to print the page",
        D: "Defines a caption at the bottom of an image",
      },
      correctAnswer: "A",
    },
    {
      questionId: 10,
      question: "What does the <form> tag do?",
      choices: {
        A: "Defines the form of a child tag in the shape of a square or circle",
        B: "Defines a pdf form that can be viewed or downloaded by the user",
        C: "Defines a dynamic text element that sets the various linguistic forms of a verb",
        D: "Defines a document section containing interative controls for submitting information",
      },
      correctAnswer: "D",
    },
  ],
};
